

Electrician office@houndelectrics.com 07788244655

Farncombe, Godalming, United Kingdom

Jason Young

Profile

Skilled, experienced and tidy electrician with experience installing and maintaining electrical systems in homes and businesses. Proven track record of identifying and correcting electrical issues from incorrectly wired heating systems to faulty smart lighting systems. Working solo and as part of a team ensuring projects are completed on time.

Employment History

NICEIC Approved Contractor at Hound Electrics, Guildford

10/2021—Present

Contracting to local builders, domestic and commercial clients. Carrying out

- EICR's
- Partial and complete rewires
- · Consumer unit changes
- · Fault finding
- Installing EV charger installation and smart home technologies.

Qualified Supervisor at Smith and Young Ltd, Guildford

04/2015-10/2021

Managing electrical projects for builders, small to large building renovations. Supervising and organising colleagues to ensure smooth completions.

- · Design, installation and certification
- · Loxone home automation

Education

Diploma, Able Skills, Dartford

03/2016-06/2022

City and Guilds 2391-52 Inspection and Testing - June 2022

City and Guilds Diploma in Electrical Installations level 2 and 3 - March 2017 to December 2018

C&G 2382-18, ElectroPass, London

03/2018

City and Guilds 18th Edition wiring regulations.

Skills

Safe Work Practices Ability to Work Under Pressure Ability to Work in a Team Troubleshooting Electrical Inspections and Repair

Hobbies

Distance running Archery Brazilian Jujitsu Fishing Coding

Courses

Loxone installers course at Loxone 06/2019

NICEIC EV Charger Installation at NICEIC 10/2021

Domestic Energy Storage Systems at Givenergy 10/2021

References

References available upon request